const mongoose = require("mongoose");
const Question = require('./../../models/Question');
require('dotenv').config();

//process.env.MONGODB_URI



const questions = [ { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 0',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 0',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 0',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 0',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev0',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 0',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d',
    difficulty: 'hard' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 1',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 1',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 1',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 1',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev1',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 1',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 2',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 2',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 2',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 2',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev2',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 2',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 3',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 3',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 3',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 3',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev3',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 3',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 4',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 4',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 4',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 4',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev4',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 4',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 5',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 5',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 5',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 5',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev5',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 5',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 6',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 6',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 6',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 6',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev6',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 6',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 7',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 7',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 7',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 7',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev7',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 7',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d',
    difficulty: 'hard' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 8',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 8',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 8',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 8',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev8',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 8',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 9',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 9',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 9',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 9',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev9',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 9',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 10',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 10',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 10',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 10',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev10',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 10',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 11',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 11',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 11',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 11',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev11',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 11',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 12',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 12',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 12',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 12',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev12',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 12',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 13',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 13',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 13',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 13',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev13',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 13',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 14',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 14',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 14',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 14',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev14',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 14',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d',
    difficulty: 'hard' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 15',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 15',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 15',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 15',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev15',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 15',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 16',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 16',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 16',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 16',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev16',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 16',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 17',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 17',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 17',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 17',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev17',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 17',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 18',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 18',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 18',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 18',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev18',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 18',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'webdev',
    question: 'Question webdev 19',
    rightAnswer: 'Right answebdev 19',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 webdev 19',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 webdev 19',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev19',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl webdev 19',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 20',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 20',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 20',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 20',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev20',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 20',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 21',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 21',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 21',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 21',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev21',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 21',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d',
    difficulty: 'hard' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 22',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 22',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 22',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 22',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev22',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 22',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 23',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 23',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 23',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 23',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev23',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 23',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 24',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 24',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 24',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 24',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev24',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 24',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 25',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 25',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 25',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 25',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev25',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 25',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 26',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 26',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 26',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 26',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev26',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 26',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 27',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 27',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 27',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 27',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev27',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 27',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 28',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 28',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 28',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 28',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev28',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 28',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d',
    difficulty: 'hard' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 29',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 29',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 29',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 29',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev29',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 29',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 30',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 30',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 30',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 30',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev30',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 30',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 31',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 31',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 31',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 31',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev31',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 31',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 32',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 32',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 32',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 32',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev32',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 32',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 33',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 33',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 33',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 33',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev33',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 33',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 34',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 34',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 34',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 34',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev34',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 34',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 35',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 35',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 35',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 35',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev35',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 35',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d',
    difficulty: 'hard' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 36',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 36',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 36',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 36',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev36',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 36',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 37',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 37',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 37',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 37',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev37',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 37',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 38',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 38',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 38',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 38',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev38',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 38',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'data',
    question: 'Question data 39',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansdata 39',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 data 39',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 data 39',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev39',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl data 39',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 40',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 40',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 40',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 40',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev40',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 40',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 41',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 41',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 41',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 41',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev41',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 41',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 42',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 42',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 42',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 42',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev42',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 42',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d',
    difficulty: 'hard' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 43',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 43',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 43',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 43',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev43',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 43',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 44',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 44',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 44',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 44',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev44',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 44',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 45',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 45',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 45',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 45',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev45',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 45',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 46',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 46',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 46',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 46',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev46',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 46',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 47',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 47',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 47',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 47',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev47',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 47',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 48',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 48',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 48',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 48',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev48',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 48',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 49',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 49',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 49',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 49',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev49',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 49',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d',
    difficulty: 'hard' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 50',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 50',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 50',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 50',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev50',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 50',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 51',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 51',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 51',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 51',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev51',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 51',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 52',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 52',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 52',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 52',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev52',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 52',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 53',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 53',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 53',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 53',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev53',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 53',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 54',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 54',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 54',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 54',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev54',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 54',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 55',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 55',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 55',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 55',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev55',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 55',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 56',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 56',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 56',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 56',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev56',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 56',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d',
    difficulty: 'hard' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 57',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 57',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 57',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 57',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev57',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 57',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 58',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 58',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 58',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 58',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev58',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 58',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' },
  { questionType: 'ux',
    question: 'Question ux 59',
    rightAnswer: 'Right ansux 59',
    wrongAnswer1: 'Wrong Answer 1 ux 59',
    wrongAnswer2: 'Wrong Answer 2 ux 59',
    wrongAnswer3: 'Wrong Answer 3 webdev59',
    photoUrl: 'photoUrl ux 59',
    created_by: '5df241030d13316631e8161d' } ];

mongoose
  .connect(process.env.MONGODB_URI, {
    keepAlive: true,
    useNewUrlParser: true,
    reconnectTries: Number.MAX_VALUE,
  })
  .then( () => {
    console.log(`Connected to database`);
    Question.collection.drop();
    Question.insertMany(questions)
      .then(_=>console.log('Questions seeded'))
      .catch(err => console.log(err));
  })
  .catch( (err) => console.error(err));